oh damn look at that oh tattoo
oh god jesus that's a traitor tattoo if
anything is guys
we're gonna look at how to trade
like a bank how do the banks trade uh so
we can take advantage of them uh i'm
gonna show you exactly
an example of basically a summarized
version of one of my strategies here
that
you guys can then use the logic of at
least and then trade similarly to a bank
and use this
to your own leverage create your own
strategy based off of that so make sure
you watch the whole thing and hit that
like button because you know it's gonna
be good
right guys so this video i'm currently
actually watching the euro usd i'm
trying to get into some trades here
these are just some marks
marks up from uh streaming here if you
guys are interested in watching those
streams
uh there is streams that i do uh most
weekdays
that you can watch watch in on so
basically what we want to be looking at
here
is one simple thing uh to get you some
logic going in
how the banks are trading here guys
basically what we're looking for
is areas of uh liquidity where
there's going to be obvious stop orders
behind these are very simple things like
okay
major pivot points or multiple highs
things like that so there's obviously
going to be liquidity above this one
because that's a major pivot point right
here i drew
let me just let me just draw
this line right here right you can see
that i've kind of made it a little bit
messy here so let's just delete all of
this for now
and we could say okay let's break down
the logic here right so a bank
sees that we're breaking up on the asia
session here
and we're rather close to this liquidity
area so what are they going to do
we're going to start gathering um we're
going to start consolidating around it
and then what they're going to think is
okay they can send some buy
orders in and you guys saw a second ago
i had one of those
diamond shapes a triangle shapes in that
because it's an idea of what i thought
could have happened right what they want
to
say is okay if we're actually looking
for shorts for today right
because the bias might be short for
today going into the
asia open once the asian bankers wake up
in the morning they say hey how we're
gonna [__] everybody over today
right so they're going to look for where
people's stops are and obviously they're
right here so what they're going to do
is they're going to buy into those stops
right and then what we want to do
is well sometimes it's going to blow
right through right basically what
happened here but we were
we were hoping that they would actually
hunt them and then break back in
so what where what the banks say is they
have so much [__] money that they
don't want to ever take a loss
so what they have to do here is this is
the last area that they're consolidating
that they have to start buying up to so
they have buy orders now in the table
so let's say that this did dump down
well that means that what they had is
they had sell orders all
resting here a large large wall of sell
orders and essentially
you know we could kind of see that that
is still true
maybe it's still true right because we
could still come down here right
it's just a larger area than i first
expected
we could still be coming down we're not
sure yet and we'll look at it in a
second
and but there is a bunch of sell orders
here
now then what we say is okay it dumps
back down
and at some point they're going to want
to take
their profits right so maybe they're
going to take their profits here at this
area where there could be resting orders
because we're bounced off or maybe
they're going to take profits way down
here or something like that
it's not too too important right maybe
they're going to take their profits
right here off that level
and this was the actual sell-off right
so maybe it's actually this is where
they took their profits
now what that profit taking then does
is create buy orders because they're
closing their cells so that's going to
create buy orders right
and it's going to start bringing it back
up now this is not a good case this is
not a good example let's actually delete
this one
but let's say because they had their
their buy orders right here
so they they sell these and then they
take profit somewhere on the sell orders
now this is one case where actually the
sell orders create more profit here
and now they can actually close these
buy orders in a profit as well
so they've just made profit on two right
and then what that's going to happen is
if they close those
those buy orders in a profit that's
going to create more sell orders and
then we can maybe take advantage of this
move here
right a more obvious situation
is where we're going to look for
something like this we're going to see a
dump off after just briefly sweeping
right and then we're going to see them
profit take at some point right we're
not sure maybe somewhere around here
right and then what's going to happen is
that's going to cause some more buys
right
now these guys they're underwater the
whole time
because they were buy orders once they
get them to break even
then often you're going to see a
rejection here right
and then that's going to be the
continuation so once again we're gonna
try to
capture this last move here right
we're gonna try to capture that last
move here because we see what basically
happens is
we look for the liquidity we say okay
the bankers bought into it
it didn't just blast through it actually
dumped off
and then they take their orders they
take their profits
and then what we have to do is we have
to make sure that we're actually able to
enter on a short here so we look for
some sort of confirmation here but this
is
all our confirmation and then we take
that last little ride of them
closing these buy orders and that's what
we're riding
guys we're trying to ride the closures
of that buy orders
and then we're just going to take a
quick little scalp right and this is how
it's going to work because then you're
going to put your stop behind there
behind wherever the level is and then
you're going to ride down that scalp and
then it's going to follow it down to the
next level down right
something along those lines all right
let's say we put it there
let's say let's let's say it dumped off
there so let's look for an actual
example of where this happened this
let's actually look this actually looks
like it's it's working right now
in what we were just explaining in the
first example
so what's happened here is we had this
level of liquidity
we hunted it we broke back in they
bought some buy orders here
buy orders went into profit and then
they had those massive sell orders
they closed the sell orders in profit
and that caused the buying
right and then they could close these
buy orders in profit as well
right and then it's going to bring it
down
so that's another another situation of
what could be happening here let's look
at um
an example of something actually working
properly here
right so here's an example on the lower
on the lower screen here
the five minute so we had some highs
here
and right at the london close right
right when the bankers were saying okay
we're all we're all done for today we
just want to do one last little trade
what they're gonna do is they're gonna
they're gonna hunt all these stops right
here they're gonna blast it up right
they're gonna hunt those stops so this
is where they bought from
right so now
they hunted all those stops and they
left those in
uh in open trade they left them as an
open order right
so now they had all these sell orders
and they filled those right here
right give it another little test and
then it dropped back down because we
weren't able to break through that
massive wall now we dump back down here
and they take their profit
let's say this is where they set their
take profits right
right down here at that level right
that's where they took their profits
and they could have done this just as
they were leaving as the london close
right
and they could have just set their take
profits there and then
these uh these trades needed to be
closed at break even right so this is
where they originally bought from
let's just draw another box and that's
where they're going to close
their breakeven trade so they have one
profitable and one break even
and then that closure causes the
movement to go down so this is what
we're trying to capture
guys so when you're seeing these hunts
this is basically what we're going to be
looking for
looking for hunts at major bank pivot
points right
and then we're going to look for the
dump off we're going to look for the
retest
of these areas of where they started
buying from
and then we simply ride down the last
little order there
now there's a very generalized statement
here it's not an exact strategy
per se but it's how banks are trading
largely right this is one of the
uh logics behind why banks are trading
or how banks are trading rather
and so you guys can kind of create
strategies based off of that
and figure out in more detail how to do
that i'm not going to dive too too much
into detail in this
in this video uh but if you guys want
more information uh
watch the streams if you guys want to
join a signal group link in the
description if you want to join free
group also link in the description
follow me on instagram see you guys next
time
[Music]
oh